A.D.
A.D.
Due to its declining birthrate of the human popula- tion,
Due to its declining birthrate of the human popula- tion,
this country has turned into a nation of cats.
this country has turned into a nation of cats.
Cat Country Japan.
Cat Country Japan.
Christmas with Everyone
Natal Bersama Semuanya
It began to snow.
Salju mulai turun.
Mugishima, look! It is snow!
Mugishima, lihat! Salju!
Please open the window.
Tolong buka jendelanya.
Here you go.
Silakan.
Ah, this is rather cold, is it not?
Ah, ini lumayan dingin, bukan?
Please close it immediately.
Tolong segera ditutup.
I figured.
Sudah kuduga.
Merry Christmas!
Selamat Hari Natal!
Today, they are celebrating Christmas at Yume's house.
Hari ini, mereka merayakan Natal di rumah temannya.
I heard there is even a Christmas tree this year.
Kudengar tahun ini ada pohon Natal juga, lho.
Do you mean that sparkling, beautiful thing?
Maksudmu benda yang berkilauan dan indah itu?
That is extremely intriguing.
Itu sungguh sangat menarik hati.
Let's play with that later.
Mari kita main dengan itu nanti.
Please stop.
Tolong jangan.
Oh my.
Owalah?
I have brought this along today.
Aku membawa ini hari ini.
Alright, shall we bring out the tree?
Baiklah, sudah waktunya kita keluarkan pohonnya.
It is finally time.
Akhirnya waktunya.
It's in the next room. Follow me.
Ada di ruangan sebelah. Ikuti aku.
Um, it looks like Sora is plotting something mischievous.
Anu, sepertinya Sora ingin menjadi bandel.
It's fine, it's fine.
Tidak apa-apa, kok.
Ta-da!
Ta-da!
Woah! A cat tower!
Wah! Cat tower!
I decided to combine the Christmas present and the tree into one!
Aku memutuskan menggabungkan hadiah Natal dan pohonnya jadi satu!
Look, look!
Lihat, lihat!
But thinking about that being our "tree",
Tapi kalau dipikir itu "pohon" kita…
makes you realize humans can't win against cats.
jadi sadar kalau manusia takkan menang lawan kucing.
Well then, everyone… see you soon.
Kalau begitu, semuanya… sampai jumpa lagi.
A cat tower…
Cat tower…
Humans understand what cats desire quite well.
Manusia paham betul apa yang didambakan kucing.
Indeed they do.
Benar sekali.
Mugishima, Merry Christmas!
Mugishima, Selamat Hari Natal!
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe was utilized
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe was utilized
: geckyzz
: geckyzz